<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pose Perfect</string>
    <string name="logo_name">Pose Perfect</string>
    <string name="slogan_name">Perfect Your Pose, Perfect Your Life.</string>

    <string name="bakasana">•Physical Benefits\n
Strengthens core, arms, and shoulders: Building core stability is essential for maintaining balance in this pose.\n
Improves balance and coordination: Regular practice enhances your ability to balance and coordinate your body movements.\n
Increases flexibility: Stretches the hips, groin, and spine, promoting overall flexibility.\n
Stimulates digestion: Massaging the abdominal organs can aid digestion.\n
Opens the chest: Improves lung capacity and posture.\n\n
•Mental Benefits\n
Boosts confidence: Successfully performing Bakasana can significantly boost self-esteem.
\nImproves focus and concentration: Maintaining balance requires intense mental focus.
\nReduces stress and anxiety: The physical challenge and mental focus can help alleviate stress.</string>

    <string name="pigeon">•Physical Benefits\n
Improves hip flexibility: Targets tight hip flexors and glutes.\n
Relieves lower back pain: Stretches the muscles around the spine.\n
Increases range of motion: Improves mobility in the hips and pelvis.\n
Aids digestion: Stimulates the abdominal organs.\n
Improves posture: By lengthening the spine and core.\n\n
•Mental Benefits\n
Reduces stress and anxiety: Deep stretching can help relax the body and mind.\n
Enhances focus and concentration: Holding the pose requires mental focus.</string>

    <string name="dancer">•Physical Benefits\n
Improves balance and coordination: Requires focused attention and body awareness.\n
Strengthens legs, core, back, and arms: The standing leg bears the body weight, while the lifted leg and arms provide counterbalance.\n
Enhances flexibility of the spine: Deepens the backbend, improving spinal mobility.\n
Opens the chest and shoulders: Promotes deeper breathing and better posture.\n
Stimulates abdominal organs: Can aid digestion.\n
Improves hip flexor flexibility: Stretches the front of the hip.\n\n
•Mental Benefits
Boosts confidence: Mastering this pose can significantly boost self-esteem.\n
Improves focus and concentration: Requires mental clarity and determination.\n
Reduces stress and anxiety: The physical challenge and mental focus can help alleviate stress.</string>

    <string name="feather">•Physical Benefits\n
Strengthens core, arms, and shoulders: Requires significant upper body strength.\n
Improves balance and coordination: Challenging to maintain equilibrium.\n
Increases flexibility: Stretches the shoulders, chest, and spine.\n
Improves circulation: Inverted position promotes blood flow to the brain.\n
Aids digestion: Can stimulate digestive system.\n\n
•Mental Benefits\n
Boosts confidence: Mastering this pose significantly boosts self-esteem.\n
Enhances focus and concentration: Requires intense mental focus.\n
Reduces stress and anxiety: Physical challenge and mental focus can alleviate stress.</string>

    <string name="firefly">•Physical Benefits\n
Strengthens core, arms, and legs: Requires significant muscular engagement.\n
Improves balance and coordination: Challenging to maintain equilibrium.\n
Increases flexibility: Stretches the hips, groin, and shoulders.\n
Opens the chest: Promotes deeper breathing.\n\n
•Mental Benefits\n
Boosts confidence: Mastering this pose significantly boosts self-esteem.\n
Enhances focus and concentration: Requires mental clarity and determination.</string>

    <string name="peacock">•Physical Benefits\n
Strengthens core, arms, and wrists: Requires significant upper body strength.\n
Improves balance and coordination: Challenging to maintain equilibrium.\n
Aids digestion: Massages abdominal organs, improving digestion.\n
Detoxifies the body: Stimulates the digestive system, aiding in detoxification.\n
Corrects posture: Strengthens the back and core, improving posture.\n\n
•Mental Benefits\n
Boosts confidence: Mastering this pose significantly boosts self-esteem.\n
Enhances focus and concentration: Requires intense mental focus.\n
Reduces stress and anxiety: Physical challenge and mental focus can alleviate stress.</string>


</resources>